Guide to the Art Torres Papers, ca. 1970-1994 M0881
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Art Torres Papers
ca. 1970-1994
M0881
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
47.5 Linear feet 97 boxes
Contains legislative files, subject files, and general files, which include a smattering of clippings, correspondence, and miscellaneous materials.
Torres, Art.
Collection Scope and Content Summary
Contains legislative files, subject files, and general files, which include a smattering of clippings, correspondence, and miscellaneous materials.
Biography
Art Torres was a California state senator for many years. After retiring from the Senate, he became the President of the Democratic Party of California.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Art Torres, 1995.
Access Restrictions
None.
Mexican Americans
Collection Contents
- Senate Bill 742, Education (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 743, Schools (minutes of silence) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 817, Bail (Penal Code) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 820, Prisoners (Penal Code) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 821, Youth (Penal Code) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 863, Fiscal Affairs (health block grant) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 865, Schools (attendance at community colleges) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1036, Low-Level Radioactive Waste (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1155 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 1156, Automobile Insurance (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 1158, Acupuncturists (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 1234, Death Penalty (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Senate Bill 1159, California Rapid Transit District (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1255, Criminal Law (prisoners) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1440 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1497, Small Business Venture Capital (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1497, Unitary Tax Exemption (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1499, Grants (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1620 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1622, Age Discrimination: Condos (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1621, Criminal Law: Prisoners (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1753 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1755 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1756, Model Arts (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1757, Victims of Toxic Waste Compensation (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1758, Standardized Testing (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1853 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1855, Evidence Code (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1854 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1856 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1857 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1858, Sunsetting of Education Programs (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1859, Long Term Care, Spot Bill (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1892 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1909, Outdoor Advertising (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1977, Child Safety Seat Restraints (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 2178, Chiropractor Health Exams in Schools (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 2072 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2179 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2180, Pharmacies (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2181, Educational Clinics (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2245, Asbestos in Schools (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Senate Constitutional Amendment 9, Commission on Judicial Appointments (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 58, Consolidation of State Agencies (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Senate Joint Resolution 12, Space Station Program (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Senate Constitutional Amendment 30, School Bonds (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 91 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Senate Joint Resolution 28, Vincent Chin (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Senate Joint Resolution 45 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Senate Joint Resolution 46 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Senate Joint Resolution 48 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 246, TVQ Bill (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 313 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 366 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 439, Hospital Peer Review (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 859 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 859, Milk Products: Safety (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1044, Psychotherapist - Patient Privilege (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 1045, La County Transportation Commission (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1046, Economic Poisons: Adverse Effects (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1047, Pesticides: Safety (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1049, Safety Retirement (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1357, Transfer in Fraud of Creditors (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1412, Cosmetology (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1413, Contractors: Home Improvement Salespersons (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1451, Hazardous Substance Cleanup Bond Act of 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1468 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 1452, Japanese American National Museum (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1524, Victims: Board Case, Decision Justification (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1525, Victims: Board of Control - Int. on Late Payments (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1611, Poisoning (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1629, Restroom Equity (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1630, Education (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1700, Water Contingency Contracts (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1703, Agricultural Imports (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1823 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 1846, Elder Abuse Hotline (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 1847, Motor Vehicle Fees (spot) (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 1701, Farm Land Foreclosure (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1702, Consumer awareness, Buy California (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2054 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2120 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2121, Radioactive Waste, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 2293 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 2294 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 2375, Hazardous Waste Control Account (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 2423 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 2424, Hazardous Waste Enforcement (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 2425 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 2426, Health Care (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Senate Bill 2487 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Senate Bill 2519 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Senate Bill 2520, Education (spot) (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Senate Constitutional Amendment 38 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 28, Student Aid Commission (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 43 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 66 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 72 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 80, Calif. Commission on Aviation and Airports (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 81, Victims of Crimes (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 95, Los Angeles Central Library (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Senate Joint Resolution 19 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Senate Joint Resolution 27 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Senate Joint Resolution 31 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Senate Joint Resolution 40, Food Embargoes (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Senate Joint Resolution 46 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 9, English Language Opportunity Act (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Senate Bill 52 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Senate Joint Resolution 50, Exporting New Drugs (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 59 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 64, Aerobics Instructors, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 65 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 66 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Unbacked Bill (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 76 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 67, Cosmetology, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 88 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 192 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 192, Immigration Consultants, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 196 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Senate Bill 352 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Senate Bill 432, F1 Visa Foreign Students (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Senate Bill 491 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Senate Bill 492 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Senate Bill 530 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Senate Bill 580, Hazardous Waste: Administrative Penalties, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Senate Bill 672 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Senate Bill 765 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Senate Bill 766 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Senate Bill 839, Acupuncture (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Senate Bill 840 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Senate Bill 841 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Senate Bill 842 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Senate Bill 843 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Senate Bill 844 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1036 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1037 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1077 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1402 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1374 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1497 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1548 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1583 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 1584, Federal Immigration Act of 1936, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 1585 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 1586 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Senate Bill 1612 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Senate Bill 1656, Homeless: Child Welfare, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Senate Bill 1657 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Senate Bill 1797 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Senate Bill 1829 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Senate Bill 1840 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Senate Bill 1841 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Senate Bill 1842 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Senate Bill 1923 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Senate Bill 2092 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Senate Bill 2093 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Senate Bill 2095 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Senate Bill 2165 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Senate Bill 2166 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2167 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2256 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2423 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2424 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 2425, Anatomical Gifts, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 2426 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 23 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 2481 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 2482 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 2483 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2484 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2485 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2486 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2487 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 2587 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 2588 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 2589 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 2590 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 2692 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 2693 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 2729 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 26 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Senate Bill 2742 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Senate Bill 2792 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Senate Bill 2793 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Senate Bill 2794 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 75 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Senate Bill 2797 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2841 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2896 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Senate Joint Resolution 12 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Senate Joint Resolution 28 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Senate Joint Resolution 33 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 3X (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 4X (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 6X (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 7X (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 1741 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 1747 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Senate Bill 1753 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Senate Bill 1756 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Senate Bill 54, Vernon Incinerator, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 55, Amerasian Bill, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 68, Educational Clinics, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 68 (continued) (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 69 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 89 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1757 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1758 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1759 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1760 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1796 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 2094 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 181, Wrongful Termination: Employment, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 182, Social Worker Authority: Child Protection, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 257, Leaves of Absence, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 259, Child Services Masterplan, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 428, Vicious Dogs, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 258, Community Recreation, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 429, Calif. Waste Management Board, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 475, Hazardous Waste Materials Fees, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 345, Global Warming (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 323, High Rise Sprinklers, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 323 (continued) (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 260, Children's Services Commission, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 304, Computer Crimes, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 288, Classified School Employees (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 361, Rainforest Study, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 368, Nursing Hours, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 425 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 387 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 415, Proposition 65, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 427, Rainforests (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 427 (continued) (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 533 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 416 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 775, Calif. Investment Corporation (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 995, Emergency Housing, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 531, Civil Rights: Civil Penalties, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 532, Attorney General: Duties, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 996, Solid Waste / Air Quality, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 653, Gans Intervention Counseling, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 654, Acupuncture Insurance Benefits, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1049, Emergency Response (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1050 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 776, Foreclosure: Hazardous Substance, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1097 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1051 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1599, SAT, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1112, Controlled Substance: Diversion, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1113, Pesticides, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1415, CPEC Study: CC Transfers, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1357, Hate Violence: K-12 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1449 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1114 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1416, Standardized Tests: Higher Education, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1552 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1571, Bidding Preferences: CA Companies, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1588 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1627, Central Environment Disease Control, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1648, Community College Transfers, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 1649, Transfer Centers, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1652, CSU: Nonacademic Employees, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1710, Fire Sprinkler Bond, 1989 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1741, Biodegradables, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1804, Nonhazardous Waste Classification, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1806, Air Pollution: Cogeneration and Resource Recovery, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 1805, Solid Waste: Transformation, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1823, Pest Control: Eradication (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1845, Water Quality: Bay and Ocean Discharge Fees, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1843, Real Property, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1846, Child Care, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1850, Southern California Metropolitan Transportation Commission, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2225, California Data Needs, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1857, Hazardous Materials, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1875, Philippines, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1884, Aboveground Crude Oil Storage Tanks: Drug Testing, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 1887, Environmental Quality, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1920, L.A. River: Parkway, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 1975, Education: Specialized Secondary Schools (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2008, Museum: Chinese Heritage and Culture, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2083, Wages: Civil Actions, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2083 (continued) (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2256, CA Commission on Aviation and Airports: Creation (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 1919, CA Child Day Care Facilities Act, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2261, Medi-Cal: Provider Reimbursement, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2262, Hazardous Materials: Schoolsites, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 2441, Cal Welcoming Act, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 2263, Hazardous Materials: Emergency (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2308, Criminal Procedure: Minor's Testimony, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2442, Hazardous Materials M[anageme]nt, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2443, Local Government Empty: Labor Disputes (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2445, Standardized Tests, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2450, Postsecondary Ed[ucational] Institutions Reporting Requirements, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2696, CA National Guard: Helicopter, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2506, Office of Self-Esteem Ombudsman (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2605, School Lunches, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2606, Attorneys (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2771, Hazardous Substances (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2747 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 2641, Home Equity Scam, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2746, Public Social Services: Homeless, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2772, Pest Control: Inspection Stations, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2773, Air Pollution: Toxic Hot Spots, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2776, Toxic Air Contamination, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2845, Minority Tenure Files: Discrimination Disclosures, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2774, Waste Exports, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2775, Historic Building Code, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Senate Joint Resolution 75 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2882, Alcohol Programs, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 2843, Master Plan: Minority Faculty, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2844, Tenure File Retainment: Misdemeanor, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 2856, Healthcare Services: Provider data, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 9, J[oin]t Committee Reauthorization, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2879, L.A. Memorial Coliseum, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 34, PERS: Military Service Credits, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 2900, California Airline Service Authority, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 79, Antarctica, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 2880, Airports, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 103, U.C. Students, Retention Resolution, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Senate Concurrent Resolution 112, Cleanup of Toxic Contamination, San Gabriel Valley, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Senate Joint Resolution 10, Refugee Admission Quotas, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Senate Joint Resolution 29, El Salvador, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Senate Joint Resolution 42, National Endowment for the Arts, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Senate Joint Resolution 71, Rain Forest Destruction, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 13X (Torres), Bonds, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 25X (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 19X (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Senate Bill 26X (Box 46, Folder 2)
- New Initiatives for a New Los Angeles: Final report, Dec 9, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Unauthorized Migration: Report, July 1990 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Proposition 166: Basic Health Care Coverage, Sept 29, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- California's Environment and the International Agenda, Dec 10-14, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 65, One Last Chance - A Final Report, Jan 1993 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- 1989 Northern California Earthquake: Legislative response, Nov 8, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Report by the Auditor General of California, August 1992 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Senator Art Torres (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Senate Committee on Insurance, Claims and Corporations, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Senate Committee on Toxics and Public Safety Management, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Senate Task Force on L.A. Renewal (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Press / Editorial (Box 47, Folder 6)
- California's Aboveground Petroleum Storage Act, Oct 1990 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Senator Torres, Statement, Oct 4, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- 'Californians Together', July 1993 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- 1989 Northern California Earthquake, Nov 2, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Interim Hearing, Oct 29, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Latinos in California, Feb 6, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- California Economy, Feb 4, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- The 1991 East Bay Firestorm, Nov 14, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- 1986 Press Releases (Box 48, Folder 2)
- 1987 Press Releases (Box 48, Folder 3)
- 1988 Press Releases, File no. 3 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- 1988 Press Releases, File no. 4 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- 1988 Press Releases, File no. 1 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- 1987 Press Releases (continued) (Box 48, Folder 7)
- 1989 Press Release (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Press Release 1989 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 112, Letter Delivery (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Ladera Heights Hearing (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Torres Appointed to Chair Leg[islative] Panel Investigating Police Conduct (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Media [?] Advisory (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Legislation to Overhaul Amnesty (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Media Advisory - Auto Insurance, Background on Senate Bill 239, June 11, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 340, Torres Introduces Auto Insurance Reform Bill, June 13, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 1335, Torres, Floor Debate, July 8, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 6, Torres, July 9, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 6, Approval, June 16, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 1764, June 24, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 1335, Press Advisory, June 5, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Major Health Care Legislation (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Immigrant Workforce Preparation, June 4, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Senate Establishes Special Task Force to Renew L.A., May 21, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Legislation to Boost Workforce Skills of Recent Immigrants Clear Key Fiscal Committee (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Media Advisory Response Press Conference - Immigration, May 19, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Senate Bill 1335, Peace Office Conduct, May 8, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Torres Proposes Five Point Plan to Rebuild L.A. after Riots, May 4, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Police Officer Conduct Hearing, May 1, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Senator Torres Proposes Term Limit for State Insurance Commissioner, April 28, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Insurance Chairman Torres to Visit Earthquake Site, April 27, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Senate Judiciary to Vote on Major Police Reform Measure, April 14, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Pasa Comite del Senado, April 13, 1992, Spanish (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Senate Bill 20, Bill Hearing, April 1, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Senate Bill 2030, Statement, March 26, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Full Senate to Hear Credit Life Insurance Measure, March 19, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Torres Announces Legis[lation?] on Police Conduct, March 18, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Torres, Community Announce Police Conduct Legis[lation?], March 17, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- California Health Reform Act of 1992 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Media Advisory, March 17, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Insurance Committee to Hear Credit Life and Earthquake Measures, March 4, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Credit Life Insurance Clears Key Senate Panel, Bill to Reform, March 4, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Torres Announces Creation of Sub. Committee for Non-Licensed Carriers, March 3, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Insurance Comm[ittee] to Hold Hearing on Earthquake Insurance, March 2, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Note: Box contains clippings. (Box 50)
- Insurance Comm[ittee], March 2, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Torres Students Announce Legislation to Block Student Fee Increase, Feb 20, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Students to Announce Legislation to Curb Student Fees, Feb 19, 1992 (Box 50, Folder 3)